Osterman, Melvin Papers 6211
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Melvin Osterman Papers
1932-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Osterman, Melvin
6211
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records.
6169911
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D. Mordente, November 28, 2007
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Unemployment insurance -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- Government employees -- New York (State); New York (State) -- Officials and employees; Osterman, Melvin H., 1934-; Civil Service Employees Association (N.Y.); Mental Hygiene Employees Association, Inc.; New York (State). Office of Employee Relations.; New York (State). Public Employment Relations Board.; New York (State). Task Force on Equal Employment Opportunities for Women in New York State Government.; New York (State). Governor's Office of Employee Relations.
6169911
- Case and Points 1: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; White & Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Case and Points 2: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; White & Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Case and Points 3: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; New York State (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Case and Points 4, Part 1: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; CSEA & Helsby (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Case and Points 4, Part 2: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; CSEA v. Helsby (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Case and Points 6, Part 1: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; Wakshull v. Helsby (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Case and Points 6, Part 2: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; Wakshull v. Helsby (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Case and Points 6, Part 3: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; Wakshull v. Helsby (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Case and Points 6, Part 4: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr.; Wakshull v. Helsby (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Case and Points 7, Part 1: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Case and Points 7, Part 2: Melvin H. Osterman, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- NYS Office of Employee Relations: Employee Relations Manual (Box 3, Folder 3)
- NYS Public Employment Relations Board Binder (Box 3, Folder 4)
- NYS Court of Appeals: Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. v. The Public Employment Relations Board (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Arbitration and Fact Finding Binder (Box 3, Folder 6)
- MHO 1973-1976 Negotiations: Offers, Data, Minutes (Box 4, Folder 1)
- MHO 1973-1976 Negotiations: State and CSEA Demands (Box 4, Folder 2)
- NYS Office of Employee Relations: Grievance and Discipline Arbitrations I (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NYS Office of Employee Relations: Grievance and Discipline Arbitrations II (Box 4, Folder 4)
- NYC Public Employment Relations Board: NYS Employees Council 50 & NYS Civil Service Employees Association, Inc.- Trial Memorandum (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Comparison by Article of State-CSEA Institutional Services Unit Agreements 1970-2, 1972-3, 1973-6, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 1974 Departmental Impasse Factfinding NYC Public Service Commision & The Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Compendium of Agreements Between the State of NY and the CSEA 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Review of the Unemployment Insurance Financing in NYS: Report of the Governor's Committee on Unemployment Insurance Financing (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Mental Hygiene Employees Association, Inc. & Sarah E. Green vs. Edward V. Regan & Meyer S. Frucher and The Civil Service Employees Association Inc.- Brief of Intervenor- Respondent (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Mental Hygiene Employees Association, Inc. & Sarah E. Green vs. Edward V. Regan & Meyer S. Frucher and The Civil Service Employees Association Inc.- Brief of Petitioners- Appellants (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Mental Hygiene Employees Association, Inc. & Sarah E. Green vs. Edward V. Regan & Meyer S. Frucher and The Civil Service Employees Association Inc.- Brief for Respondents (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Mental Hygiene Employees Association, Inc. & Sarah E. Green vs. Edward V. Regan & Meyer S. Frucher and The Civil Service Employees Association Inc.-Record on Appeal (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Memorandum: Layoff Procedure 1/15/1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Taylor Law Task Force Report to Governor Malcolm Wilson 5/8/1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Report of the Joint Legislative Committee on Classification of Positions in the Civil Service (1932) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Your Benefits as a NYS Employee (A Brief Summary) NYS Dept. of Civil Service Personnel Services Division 9/1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Letter to Ersa Poston, Commissioner of Civil Service 7/2/1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- A Proposal for NYS: Personal Annual Reports Packet (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Labor Relations Manual for the General Cable Corp.: Vacations (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Bayonne Labor Relations Handbook: Hours & Overtime (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Task Force on Equal Employment Opportunities for Women in NYS Government 12/1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Report of the Committee on Ethnic Data Systems Administered by the Department of Civil Service (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Letters to Esra Poston: Oct.-Nov., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Task Force on Equal Employment Opportunities for Women in NYS Government Interim Report: Aug. 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Equal Opportunity Plan (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Attachments to Remarks of Melvin H. Osterman, Jr. (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Letter to Mr. Lanning Mosher 1/17/1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Letter to Mr. Osterman, Jr. 12/12/1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Data Needs for 1975 Salary Negotiations (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Security Services Unit 1972 Summary (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Comparison of Basic Retirement Provisions for Public Employees 6/1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Memorandum: 1975 CSEA Negotiations (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Memorandum: Productivity in the Federal Govt. 1/18/1974 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- 1985 Coalition Demands Prepared by the Civil Service Employees Assoc., Inc. (Box 5, Folder 27)
- NYS Governor's Office of Employee Relations State Proposals for Negotiations b/t NYS and the Civil Service Employee Assoc., Inc. Administrative Services Unit (Box 5, Folder 28)
- NYS Governor's Office of Employee Relations State Proposals for Negotiations b/t NYS and the Civil Service Employee Assoc., Inc. Institutional Services Unit (Box 5, Folder 29)
- NYS Governor's Office of Employee Relations State Proposals for Negotiations b/t NYS and the Civil Service Employee Assoc., Inc. Operational Services Unit (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Documents for Fact-Finder, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Documents for Fact-Finder, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Public Employee Relations Board Brief of Employer, State University of NY (Box 5, Folder 33)
- NYS Court of Appeals: Assoc. of NYS Civil Services Attorneys, Inc. v. the Public Employment Relations Board- Memorandum of Respondent-Employer (Box 5, Folder 34)
- NY Supreme Court: The Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. v. The Public Employment Relations Board & Abe Lavine- Plaintiff's Brief (Box 5, Folder 35)
- NY Supreme Court: The Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. v. The Public Employment Relations Board & Abe Lavine- Defendant's Memorandum of Law (Box 5, Folder 36)
- NY Supreme Court Respondents' Appendix C. (Box 5, Folder 37)
- NYS Requested Appropriations for the Fiscal Year April 1, 1974- March 31,1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- NYS Material (Box 5, Folder 39)